research.att.com 2018-06-14

# Privacy Policy for all AT&T Inc. Websites

This Privacy Policy applies to the websites for AT&T Inc. and information collected through those websites.  AT&T products and services are provided or offered by subsidiaries and affiliates of AT&T Inc. under the AT&T brand or other brands and not by AT&T Inc.  Those subsidiaries and affiliates have their own privacy policies that apply to their products, services, and websites.  This Privacy Policy applies only to the websites for AT&T Inc. (“AT&T Inc. websites” or “these websites”). By using AT&T Inc. websites, you accept and agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy (“Policy”). If you do not agree to this Policy, please do not use these websites.

**Information we collect through AT &T Inc. websites**

We automatically collect information about how you use these websites and what device or devices you use to do so through the use of cookies, web beacons, and other technologies.  For example, these websites automatically record website usage information including your IP address, browser type, operating system, and device type used to access the website.  This information does not identify you personally, and we do not use this information to track or record information about individuals through these websites.

**How we use the information we collect**

We use the data collected through these websites for a variety of purposes including to better understand how people use each website, to prevent fraud, and to improve the effectiveness, security and integrity of the website. We may also use the data to protect and enforce our agreements and property rights, to comply with court orders, legal processes or respond to regulatory or other similar requests.

**We share the information with**

  * Our subsidiaries and affiliates.
  * Vendors and agents performing services on our behalf.
  * Third parties but only in aggregate form or as may be required by law.

**Data storage and retention**

Data we collect through the AT&T Inc. websites may be processed and stored in the United States, or in other countries where we or our affiliates or service providers process data. We take steps to ensure that data is processed according to this Policy and to the requirements of applicable law of your country and of the additional countries where the data is subsequently processed.

When we transfer personal data from the European Economic Area to other countries, we use appropriate legal mechanisms to help ensure all applicable laws, rights and regulations continue to protect your data.

We keep any information we collect through these websites as long as we need it for business, tax, or legal purposes. After that, we destroy it by making it unreadable or indecipherable.

**Security of your data**

We've established electronic and administrative safeguards designed to make the information we collect from these websites secure. However, no transmission or electronic storage of information is guaranteed to be secure. We therefore urge you to always use caution when transmitting information over the Internet.

**Links to other websites**

These websites contain links to other websites and servers that are not AT&T Inc. websites. This Policy does not apply to the privacy practices or the content of such linked sites. When you link to another site, you are subject to the privacy policy of the new site.

**Changes in ownership or to the Policy**

Information collected through these websites may be shared and transferred as part of any merger, acquisition, sale of company assets, or transition of service to another provider. This also applies in the unlikely event of an insolvency, bankruptcy, or receivership in which customer and user records would be transferred to another entity as a result of such a proceeding.

We may update this Policy as necessary to reflect changes we make and to satisfy legal requirements. Updates to this Policy will be posted to these websites.  We’ll post a prominent notice of material changes on these websites.

**Information for our California customers**

Website data collection: We don’t knowingly allow other parties to collect personally identifiable information about your online activities over time and across third-party websites when you use our websites unless we have your consent.

**Do Not Track notice** : We don’t currently respond to Do Not Track and similar signals.  Please go to [All About Do Not Track](https://allaboutdnt.com/) for more information.

Any customer who wishes to request further information about our compliance with these requirements, or who has questions or concerns about our privacy practices and policies, can email us at privacypolicy@att.com, or write to us at AT&T Privacy Policy, Chief Privacy Office, 208 S. Akard, Room 1031, Dallas, TX 75202.

**Contact Us**

Need to update your information? We’re happy to help you review and correct the information we have. For more information, or for help with other questions, you can:

  * Email us at [privacypolicy@att.com](mailto:privacypolicy@att.com).
  * Write to us at AT&T Privacy Policy, Chief Privacy Office, 208 S. Akard, Room 1031, Dallas, TX 75202.

For other inquiries, customer service contact numbers can be found at att.com.
